The End No way we got it!
That treasure's been at the bottom
of the ocean for a hundred years!
And now whatever's in it is ours!
Hey, stay calm.
We gotta get it on the boat
before we start celebrating.
Yeah, I know, I know.
Up we go!
That thing looks too long and
narrow to be a treasure chest.
Just do your job!
You're lifting it too high!
Okay, on three.
One, two, three!
All right.
Come on, crack it open, O 'Rish.
Hold on, wait.
This is bizarre.
It seems like this thing
was locked from the inside.
Who the hell cares?
Just bust it open!
Just give me a sec.
Something's written on it.
D-I-O. D-O?
Is that someone's name?
I don't care!
Just freaking open it up!
The sun's about to go down and I don't
want to be counting treasure in the dark!
Okay, I hear ya. Hmm.
I'm gonna go get the blowtorch.
And then we can start
dividing up our loot!
On a day like any other, a motorboat
was found adrift and abandoned.
The craft was largely undamaged
and showed no signs of struggle.
In the galley,
three cups of coffee sat half-full,
and on deck, an iron chest,
its lock melted away,
lay open and empty.
But the chest's unusual shelter-like
chambers baffled discoverers,
who believed it to have once
contained a vast treasure.
But interest waned, and before
long, the chest was forgotten.
Jotaro Kujo, 17 years old
and 195 centimeters tall.
His father is a Japanese jazz
musician, currently on tour.
His mother is an American
of British descent.
Yes, all of that is correct,
and Jotaro is definitely my son.
It seems like all his
friends call him Jojo.
Guess they decided to take
the Joe from his first
name and the Joe from his
last name and combine them.
Oh man, that's really lame.
I need to know.
Exactly how many people did Jotaro kill?
No, I take it back.
I don't want to know.
Settle down.
Nobody said anything
about him killing people.
He got into a fight, that's all.
The truth is, the thugs he tangled with
were all armed with nunchucks and knives.
He fought four punks, one being an
ex-boxer, and he broke 15 of their bones.
And he busted their balls.
Sorry if that was crude.
He put all of them in a hospital.
Things could have gone a lot worse.
He's got to be shown the
severity of his actions.
Okay.
The real issue is what happened afterward.
Copy this and pass it around.
Yes, sir.
I got to tell you, that son
of yours is a strange one.
Huh?
Okay, follow me.
I'll show you the way.
Thank you for everything.
Look, you can thank me
by taking your kid home.
So then, does that mean
you're releasing him?
Well, we can't keep him in here forever.
Okay.
By the way, ma 'am, I have to tell you,
your Japanese is really quite good.
Just how long have you
been living in Japan?
For 20 years now.
Well, that explains it then.
Good work, man.
This place has been overrun lately.
We've got an entire backlog of criminals
that we aren't even able to find cells for.
We're almost there, ma 'am.
Your son's just up ahead.
Jotaro!
Throw the ball to mom!
That's it. Good boy.
Do your best at that track
meet tomorrow. I will.
Jotaro, you did it.
Let's go out to eat and celebrate.
Nothing's as good as your cooking, Mom.
Jotaro, Jotaro, Jotaro, Jotaro, Jotaro!
Shut up!
Get out of my face, you bitch!
I promise you he's a
very sweet boy he's just
not capable of doing
something so appalling.
Hey on your feet Kujo
you're being released
what part of go home don't you understand?
Listen, Mom, you can leave.
I'll be staying here for a while.
Seems I've been possessed
by an evil spirit,
and I've no idea what'll make me do next.
During that fight, it took
all I had just to stop it.
So do everyone a favor
and leave me in this cage.
Jeez, for crying out loud, do
you see what I'm talking about?
We're trying to release
him, but he refuses to go.
I'm sorry to have to ask you this,
but are you sure everything's
all right with your boy upstairs?
This isn't a hotel, you know, ma 'am.
Come on, let us change cells, please!
Stop lying about the evil spirit thing!
All right, all right, that's enough!
Oh, you shut up!
Is he?
Seriously?
What are you doing with
a beer in a jail cell?
How did you even get that in there?
I told you.
I've got an evil spirit.
And sometimes it likes to bring me things.
What the hell?
He's written Shonen Jump
while listening to a radio.
Sir, I mean, how is this even possible?
We have a major problem here.
Hold it.
This might not be enough to make
you guys keep me locked up in here.
But I'll show you how
evil the spirit is anyway.
Maybe then you'll see why letting
me out of here is a bad idea.
That's my gun he has in his hand!
But howdy!
That's really bad!
You didn't see it just now?
Well, if you guys didn't see my
evil spirit, then watch this.
No! Jotaro!
It's like there's someone behind me
that bound itself to me not long ago.
Jotaro's grandfather
Joseph has strange powers.
But what's happening to my son?
Papa!
Hmm?
Over here, Papa! Over here!
Holly!
Out of my way!
Oh, I can't believe you're here!
Thank you for coming.
Hey, you're my one and only daughter,
and if you tell me you
need me to be somewhere?
then just give me a day
and I'll cross the globe.
Did Mom come?
She didn't like me leaving,
but I just told Susie that it was
official Joestar Corporation business,
and I had to go.
Thanks, Papa.
Holly.
Hey, the greetings over
let go of me already.
No, I don't wanna it's been forever
since you've held me look at yourself.
Come on.
You're a 45 year old woman. Let go.
Oh now you've done it.
I'm gonna
Hey, what are you clowns staring at?
Don't look.
I'll take your bag.
By the way, Holly, about Jotaro.
You sure he used the word evil spirit?
Oh, my poor little boy.
Yes, the policeman said they
couldn't see it, but I saw it.
It's like he had a third arm.
And then he reached out
and grabbed the gun.
And when this arm came out, no one
else there could see it but you?
That's right.
And aside from Jotaro saying that
he's been possessed, you're okay?
Did anything happen to you?
I feel totally fine.
But what do I do about Jotaro?
He says he won't leave that cell
until he finds the cause of all this.
What am I going to do, Papa?
There, there, my darling daughter.
You've got Joseph Joestar with you now.
No need to worry. Thank you.
Now let's go see my grandson.
Jotaro can explain this himself.
It's getting spookier.
He's got more stuff in his cell now.
And he's violent.
If something is possessing him,
it's definitely not something nice.
If word of this gets out to my superiors,
I'll lose my job in a heartbeat for sure!
He's no longer your problem.
I'll be taking my grandson home now.
Your grandson?
Hold it!
That's far enough!
You're better off just
staying where you are!
It's dangerous!
Convince him to leave him
where you're standing!
I'll take my chances!
Now step aside and leave him to me!
We won't be held as possible!
Move it!
Jotaro!
This is your grandfather!
Whatever's happened,
he'll be able to help you!
Please come out and talk to him!
Come out.
It's time to go home.
Get lost.
I didn't ask you to come here.
You really think you can help me?
An old man like yourself?
Sorry you came all the way from New
York, but nobody can help me, Gramps.
Huh?
Wait that's the pinky from
my prosthetic left hand
when was he able to take
it so Did you see it or
even feel it that's the
evil spirit stay away from
me or you'll Lose what's
left of your life I've
never seen anything like
this he was able to Deceive
me right off the bat that's
unbelievable I'm afraid
I know exactly What Jotaro's
evil spirit is but I
don't think explaining it
to him will do any good.
He'll understand his situation much
better if he sees it with his own eyes.
Actually, in order for him to
truly know the danger he faces,
he needs to experience it physically.
All right, Avdol, it's your turn now.
I'd like you to meet an Egyptian
friend I met a few years ago.
Say hello to Avdol.
Do what you need to just
get my grandson to leave
this damn cell back off
you look strong enough.
But do you really think
I'd let someone chase me
out of here just because
you told them to do it?
I don't work like that
in fact all you've done
now is made me want to
stay here even more.
I'm afraid this may get
a little bit rough but in
a few minutes he'll be
riddled with so much pain.
But he'll be begging you
to let him out of here.
Just do what you gotta do.
Papa!
You can't be serious! Wait a sec!
We can't let you turn this!
Sip it, pig! Yes, sir!
This is...
That's right.
Avdol also has what you'd
call an evil spirit.
An evil spirit under the
complete command of Avdol's will.
And his name is...
Magician's Red!
It's hot.
I feel like I'm on fire.
My arms, they're burning.
What are these evil spirits?
What's Cujoh doing?
Why's he flattening himself
against the back wall?
Yeah, I don't get it.
But do you feel how hot
it's getting in here?
Look at those numbers!
That's insane!
What's happening?
Aha!
There it is!
It's finally shown itself!
And the fact that it's so clearly
visible means it's incredibly strong!
Let's do this.
I can't believe he's able to make it
manifest so distinctly well done your evil
spirit is impressive too so tell me grandpa
you know about these evil spirits of
course I do Mr Joestar when you asked me
to help get your grandson out of this jail
cell I had planned on going easy on the
boy But in light of his tremendous power,
I'm reconsidering that.
Just one misstep could
put us all in danger.
Tell me if you want me to stop.
If not, I'll resort to a use of force that
can land your grandson in the hospital.
Like I said, do what you gotta do.
Yes, sir!
Grand Bind!
Huh? What the...
What's up with this heat?
Yeah, what the hell's going on?
None of this makes any sense!
Papa, that's enough!
What are you doing to Jotaro?
Holly, be a good girl and let
Papa finish what he started, okay?
I can't breathe.
The evil spirit is withdrawing.
The heat is restricting his breathing,
which causes the evil spirit to weaken.
And now for the truth.
This may seem like an evil
spirit, but it's far from it.
Jotaro,
this thing you believe has
possessed you is actually
a powerful vision created
by your own life energy.
This vision will always
appear standing by your side.
And because of that, we call it a stand.
A stand?
Remember Aesop's fable.
The cold wind made the
Traveler pull his coat tighter,
but the heat forced him to admit defeat.
Ready to leave your cage now, Jojo?
I said it before, I'm staying.
I keep hurting other people
without even knowing I'm doing it.
Until that stops, I'm staying here.
It's nice to meet someone like
me, but if you keep this up,
you'll die.
He just broke the damn toilet! Hey!
That's destruction of property!
You had your chance.
All right, Master.
Don't say I didn't warn you!
What the hell?
Why'd you suddenly turn your back on me?
We're not done!
Mr.
Joestar, he's left his jail cell.
I've accomplished what
you asked me to do, right?
So now what you got me huh not
exactly i did have every intention of
sending you to the hospital but you're
stronger than i had expected and
if i kept going with this steel rod
just what would you have done do
not underestimate my stand magician's
red it could have easily melted
that rod midair into a worthless
puddle the power avdol has is exactly
the same as yours if you want to
know more about this evil spirit
you'll need to leave this jail thank
you
thank you
jotaro i'm glad you
finally left that awful jail cell why
are you such an annoying bitch. Okay.
I don't know.
Hey, how dare you address
your own mother that way?
And what kind of language is that?
And stop smiling, Holly.
You'll only encourage it.
Okay.
Hey, Grandpa. One question.
There's something that I can't
quite wrap my brain around.
You seem to know all about this evil?
spirit, the stand, whatever
you want to call it.
But how do you know
this? Hmm.
How do I know?
I guess I did come All the
way from New York to explain
it to you but in order for
you to fully Understand
the whole history of it
I must start from the
beginning this is Part of
the legacy of the Joestar
family take a look at these
pictures what Are these
about that coffins a
hundred years old and four
years ago it was Pulled
out of the Atlantic off
the coast of Africa okay
so I did a little research.
My grandfather, Jonathan Joestar, your
great-grandfather, died while at sea.
Turns out this exact same coffin was
on that boat with him when he died.
When they discovered it four
years ago, it was empty.
But I know exactly what was inside it.
Avdol and I are trying to
locate him as we speak. Hold on.
Did you say him?
Are you suggesting there was
a person inside that thing?
Come on, how could a human being stay
buried underwater for a hundred years?
Because that person is evil
incarnate and his name is Dio.
And now that he has been awakened
from his hundred year slumber?
it is our fate to fight that man.
What the hell does that face mean?
And don't you turn your back on me
like this has nothing to do with you.
Look, you old man, this face
means your story is so lame?
I don't know what to say.
What?
Old man?!
Avdol, was it?
I don't know you, but you
are one arrogant bastard.
And as for you,
old man, did you really expect me to
fall for an unbelievable story like that?
I know the story sounds far-fetched,
but wouldn't you also say our evil
spirits are equally unbelievable?
Hmm.
Think what you want, but soon you
will have no choice but to believe it.
If you want me to tell you how I know that
Dio exists and why I've
chosen to go after him,
the best way to explain it is to show you.
See, the truth of it is,
I myself had a rather startling
revelation that prompted all of this.
About a year ago, I suddenly
obtained a stand of my own.
What did you say?
Raps, what did you...
Get ready!
Let me introduce...
My stand!
Did you see it?
The thorns that came out of my hand?
This is my stand.
It can reveal faraway visions
and place them on film.
The only downside is I have to bust a
30,000 yen camera every time I use it.
Excuse me.
Is everything all right here?
We're fine. Now go on.
Run along. Of course.
In a matter of seconds, a vision will
appear in this photograph, Jotaro.
and it will reveal your very destiny!
What are you talking about?
Jotaro, Polly,
have either of you ever taken the time to
look carefully at the back of your necks?
What does that mean?
You each have it, but you probably
never thought much about it.
A birthmark shaped like a star.
It turns out that we all have it.
I'll say it again.
What the hell does all this mean?
My father died when I was young,
so I asked my mother about it,
and she said he had one, too.
It seems that everyone from the Joestar
bloodline is born with this
exact same birthmark. All right.
And just what the hell is going
to turn up in that photograph?
It's our destiny, a path that
until now has been unknown.
I'm losing my patience.
Just show me the damn photo already!
Dio he shows up in all my spirit photos
and look what's just above his shoulder
from the neck of this bastard on down
is Jonathan Joestar my grandfather
this son of a bitch took over his body
a hundred years ago there was an incident
in the Atlantic Ocean all I know is
what I've learned from my grandmother,
Arina.
Somehow Dio took over the body of my
grandfather and survived.
And this much I know is certain.
This bastard is
currently hiding somewhere on
the globe, plotting something.
It's four years since he's revived
and the reason my spirit photography
and your evil spirit have manifested
since is most likely connected to Dio.
To society in general our gifts Are
considered a kind of psychic power.
I've had my stand since the
day I was born but your powers
seem bound to Dio's body or
rather Jonathan Joestar's body.
There's some sort of invisible
string that connects you all to him.
His rebirth is also your own awakening.
Your sleeping powers.
Avdol does this photograph give you any
indication to where he might be now?
No, nothing.
There's hardly anything of
note in the photo at all.
I see.
I'll take a closer look later.
Thank you. Hmm?
Oh, Hell!
I'm sorry I sprang this
all on you out of the blue.
Let's head home now. All right.
I think I'll be sticking
around for quite some time.
You mind if I stay at
your place while I'm here?
No, of course not, Papa.
Let's go, Jotaro.
Again.
Just now, a most intense feeling like
someone somewhere is watching me.
It is Jonathan's descendants.
This body is sending out some kind
of spiritual signal to his offspring.
Fine.
It must be my fate, but
fate must be purged.
It's all set.
I've taken the first step.
Jotaro!
Here is your goodbye kiss!
I'm Oryaki Kakyoin.
I just transferred here yesterday.
You idiot!
Does this look like a pen to you?
The loser is always the evil one.
I'll teach you justice.